Windows 11, XeonSilver CPU
Open Terminal or Windows Powershell
Activate napari-virtual environment
Start napari
Start micromanager (MM2)
Load OpenScan-TCSPC device configuration
Open DevicePropertyBrowser
Set a 4digit UDP Tx Port
Start napari-live-flim:FLIM Viewer Plugin
Set the UDP Rx Port
Start Live Imaging on MM2 :Mixed Pollengrain Sample
Adjust TCSPC-histogram parameters used for fitting/rendering
Photon counts per sec can be monitored in the TCSPC  parameter
Adjust the excitation laser power by changing Pockelcell voltage to 0.5mV
Adjust timebin start-stop parameters for fitting/rendering
Move the selection cursor (red) to select region of interest
Verify LMA/RLD fitting
Adjust LUT range for FLIM
Move cursor in FOV to see realtime curve fitting results
Add a phasor using "New Phasor Selection" button
The brightgreen phasor-cursor link green pixels in the FLIM image
Remove phasor LUT for non-overlapping colors
Add a second phasor cursor
The three fitting window shows red(FLIM), green(phasor1) and blue(phasor2) cursors used.
Stop Live Imaging. Restarting Imaging appears as a new layer.
Remove frame-accumulation and change optical zoom for LSM
Move stage to bring a pollengrain to the FOV
Check delta-Snapshot checkbox for singleshot and click Snapshot
The FLIM analysis will be split at the snapshot moments to generate slices